Viewers all over the world, whatever situation that you are in,
I command that pain, that affliction - you must go!!!
You affliction in the blood, you pain in the kidney,
you affliction in the liver, you pain in the muscle,
you affliction in the blood, you pain in the kidney -
you must go, in the name of Jesus!
Go!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, this is the voice of God.
I command that demon, wherever you are,
familiar spirits - I order you out, in the name of Jesus!
I order you out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 28/04/2019